Hey everyone, look who's here! It's Nono! She's staying with me at the moment and I guess since you've seen her last she can't have a void because the winter void makes it impressive. She's not in a good mood when it's raining.
Anyway, what I wanted to talk about today is some bodysuits and tights because I got a bunch of Walford Neon 40 tights I didn't show you yet.
And I have a bunch of bodysuits from Poppy Lush, a shapewear brand.
And I did a Poppy Lush video last year and I realized you were using my discount code quite a lot.
So here we go with another one.
We also have a bestseller, the Bolero this time.
Look how she's lying there, so sweet!
That little maniac. You can see her tail swishing, she's like, meh.
I don't actually want to be here but I also don't want to be alone upstairs.
Anyway, let's create some bodysuits and tights outfits.
First look and I think it's so elegant. I threw on
a choku which is really really sparkly and some
long gloves and we have the bodysuit here which is fake leather look but also has this tiny
lace peekaboos here in the bust area. I turn around.
I think it's a really really cool look. Also the corset like styling here of the bodysuit
as it is shapewear and I'm wearing size extra small it comes with a double layer fabric with
mesh on the inside to get this snug effect here this one has no padding in the bra area
but I think it makes nice boobs anyway and I love the little lace and it's actually it is
double layer lace as well and intertwined here is also some gold thread in the black so
very very festive
this is the full look with some heels and I think
this is really nice I like it it would be really great to wear at a
3D or swinger or whatever play party or model party you can add like a bunny mask here and
then you have like a very very sexy nice and elegant outfit anyway on to the next combination
another four-letter bodysuit this time without the lacy part this is a more straight um yeah
more energetic vibe here and you can see these lines here these are from the tights so without
tights you wouldn't see them that would be like a really smooth look perfect to wear under pants
under skirt as a top I think that would be really like cool corset lookalike top maybe pair it with
some black white pants also there's no padding and I think it makes a great push-up
I mean to be honest I had to really work getting that zipper closed because as the bodysuit before
this one has a zipper here on the side and it also has underwires in the bra part though no padding
Here you can see the bra part from the previous bodysuit and the underwise here and also, if I can put my hand inside here, the mesh layer which is the second layer behind the really cozy fall leather fabric which creates the shapewear effect.
I love this part here by the way it looks really fashionable that's what I
love about poppy lush shapewear it is like fashion and you're not supposed to
wear underwear beneath it to not ruin the shapewear effect like I do with the
tights here anyway I have something to put on top of it a bolero also from
poppy lush also four letters so I hope this will complement each other this is
not shapewear by the way it's just a nice jacket to put on top of all the
nice shapewear catsuits dresses and bodysuits I think it looks really really
nice together. Also again, size extra small is really working here to show the girls and
snatch in the waist. For the bolero I decided to go with size small, not extra small, to
just have something loose on top of all the tight shape waist up. A really classy look
with all the lace details here the leg cut is not as high and we also have the nice lace
transition here again also in case you're wondering you can see the tights from here
and that's why it's a bit darker down there if you're not wearing black tights underneath
and then it should be all nude and I quite like this look
once again with the gloss and glitter joker here again there's no push-up in the cups
and yes me wearing size extra small I may not be the perfect person to show shapewear but I really
had to squeeze into that one because you have to pull it up from the feet there's no zipper
so I really had to pull to get it over my hips and I think that you can definitely see that it
yeah it is really tight around the waist which is a really nice effect but anyway they have a lot
of sizes also up to bigger sizes so you can definitely check out the homepage. A four-letter
bodysuit and I'd say this is the perfect bodysuit to wear as a top just put some jeans on top of
or a skirt because it doesn't look like underwear as some of the other bodysuits
may look like. It has a wide straps here. It's also again like really snatching in
my waist. So I have to really pull it on and I've had it with some over knee boots.
I'm going to throw some accessories on. I have a belt.
Yeah, I think that looks quite nice and I'm going to use the Bolero again.
So, this is the full look.
I think it's quite nice. It's actually like more of a rock, rocky style with the belt.
It reminds me slightly of like 90s outfits. This bodysuit has a bra band on the inside which really like pulls the boobs together and makes a great cleavage but I can also close it completely for a more serious look.
Works also with the shrug which you can also wear oversized.
Though I again prefer it open more.
But that's up to you. I think that's a great basic top so to say as a shapewear bodysuit.
To complete the look really quick I put on a 4-letter skirt, pencil skirt.
And it is really I think a lot now.
but I mean you get the idea
maybe you recognize this one I've worn it in my first poppy lash video as a top with the skirt
just wanted to show it to you real quick as a pure bodysuit and maybe you recognize the v-shape here
it is basically the same than the lace bodysuit and I think that was a really cool selection
you can create awesome looks with them as tops or standalone body soups
soups why do i say body soups anyway check out my discount code for poppy large in the
description text i of course linked everything down below leave a thumbs up for this video
thanks for watching and i will see you in the next video have a nice day bye